<available_skills>
  <skill>
    <name>accessibility</name>
    <description>Use this skill for any accessibility concern: WCAG compliance (any success criterion including SC 1.3.5 autocomplete, SC 2.4.11 focus obscured), ARIA roles/attributes, screen reader behavior, axe-core or WAVE audit failures, color/non-text contrast, keyboard navigation, focus trapping/management, skip links, touch targets, VPAT reports, or accessible form patterns. Also trigger when a user asks whether a UI library (shadcn, Radix) handles keyboard interactions — but only if the question is specifically about accessibility behavior, not general usage. Do NOT trigger for general component usage questions where keyboard behavior is incidental (e.g., \"does shadcn Tooltip show on hover and focus?\" without an accessibility problem to solve).</description>
    <location>skills/accessibility/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>adr-writer</name>
    <description>Write, validate, and commit Architecture Decision Records in MADR 4.0.0 format. Use when user says 'write an ADR', 'create an ADR', 'document this decision', 'ADR for X', 'architecture decision record for X', 'record this decision', 'document the decision to use X', or wants to formally capture an architectural choice. Do NOT trigger on 'what ADR covers X?', 'show me the ADR for Y', 'does this violate an ADR?', or 'check ADR compliance' - those are lookup/audit tasks.</description>
    <location>skills/adr-writer/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>automatic-code-review</name>
    <description>Automatic semantic code review triggered after file modifications. Hook-driven skill that logs file changes via PostToolUse and runs the automatic-code-reviewer agent on Stop. Not user-invocable — triggered automatically by lifecycle hooks.</description>
    <location>skills/automatic-code-review/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>code-connect-components</name>
    <description>Connects Figma design components to code components using Code Connect. Use when user says "code connect", "connect this component to code", "connect Figma to code", "map this component", "link component to code", "create code connect mapping", "add code connect", "connect design to code", or wants to establish mappings between Figma designs and code implementations. Requires Figma MCP server connection.</description>
    <location>skills/code-connect-components/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>component-visualizer</name>
    <description>Generate interactive HTML dependency graphs for React components. Use when asked to "visualize components", "show component dependencies", "dependency graph", "component map", or "what depends on what".</description>
    <location>skills/component-visualizer/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>create-design-system-rules</name>
    <description>Generates custom design system rules for the user's codebase. Use when user says "create design system rules", "generate rules for my project", "set up design rules", "customize design system guidelines", or wants to establish project-specific conventions for Figma-to-code workflows. Requires Figma MCP server connection.</description>
    <location>skills/create-design-system-rules/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>create-tasks</name>
    <description>Creates well-formed tasks following a template that engineers can implement. Triggers on: 'create tasks', 'define work items', 'break this down', creating tasks from PRD, converting requirements into actionable tasks, feature breakdown, sprint planning.</description>
    <location>skills/create-tasks/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>figma</name>
    <description>Use the Figma MCP server to fetch design context, screenshots, variables, and assets from Figma, and to translate Figma nodes into production code. Trigger when a task involves Figma URLs, node IDs, design-to-code implementation, or Figma MCP setup and troubleshooting.</description>
    <location>skills/figma/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>figma-implement-design</name>
    <description>Translate Figma nodes into production-ready code with 1:1 visual fidelity using the Figma MCP workflow (design context, screenshots, assets, and project-convention translation). Trigger when the user provides Figma URLs or node IDs, or asks to implement designs or components that must match Figma specs. Requires a working Figma MCP server connection.</description>
    <location>skills/figma-implement-design/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>miro-mcp</name>
    <description>This skill teaches how to use Miro MCP tools effectively for creating diagrams, documents, tables, and extracting context from Miro boards. Use when the user asks about Miro capabilities, wants to create content on Miro boards, or needs to work with Miro board data.</description>
    <location>skills/miro-mcp/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>nodejs</name>
    <description>Core Node.js backend patterns for TypeScript applications including async/await error handling, middleware concepts, configuration management, testing strategies, and layered architecture principles. Use when building Node.js backend services, APIs, or microservices.</description>
    <location>skills/nodejs/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>playwright-skill</name>
    <description>Complete browser automation with Playwright. Auto-detects dev servers, writes clean test scripts to /tmp. Test pages, fill forms, take screenshots, check responsive design, validate UX, test login flows, check links, automate any browser task. Use when user wants to test websites, automate browser interactions, validate web functionality, or perform any browser-based testing.</description>
    <location>skills/playwright-skill/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>prisma</name>
    <description>Prisma ORM patterns including Prisma Client usage, queries, mutations, relations, transactions, and schema management. Use when working with Prisma database operations or schema definitions.</description>
    <location>skills/prisma/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>react</name>
    <description>Core React 19 patterns including hooks, Suspense, lazy loading, component structure, TypeScript best practices, and performance optimization. Use when working with React components, hooks, lazy loading, Suspense boundaries, or React-specific TypeScript patterns.</description>
    <location>skills/react/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>react-best-practices</name>
    <description>React performance optimization guidelines from Vercel Engineering. This skill should be used when writing, reviewing, or refactoring React code to ensure optimal performance patterns. Triggers on tasks involving React components, data fetching, bundle optimization, or performance improvements.</description>
    <location>skills/react-best-practices/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>route-tester</name>
    <description>Framework-agnostic HTTP API route testing patterns, authentication strategies, and integration testing best practices. Supports REST APIs with JWT cookie authentication and other common auth patterns.</description>
    <location>skills/route-tester/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>setup</name>
    <description>Verify environment variables, MCP servers, and LSP are configured correctly. Use when user says 'setup', 'check my setup', 'verify config', 'is everything configured', or wants to confirm their development environment is ready.</description>
    <location>skills/setup/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>shadcn</name>
    <description>Manages shadcn components and projects - adding, searching, fixing, debugging, styling, and composing UI. Provides project context, component docs, and usage examples. Applies when working with shadcn/ui, component registries, presets, --preset codes, or any project with a components.json file. Also triggers for "shadcn init", "create an app with --preset", or "switch to --preset".</description>
    <location>skills/shadcn/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>skill-creator</name>
    <description>Create new skills, modify and improve existing skills, and measure skill performance. Use when users want to create a skill from scratch, edit, or optimize an existing skill, run evals to test a skill, benchmark skill performance with variance analysis, or optimize a skill's description for better triggering accuracy.</description>
    <location>skills/skill-creator/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>skill-developer</name>
    <description>Create and manage Claude Code skills following Anthropic best practices. Use when creating new skills, modifying skill-rules.json, understanding trigger patterns, working with hooks, debugging skill activation, or implementing progressive disclosure. Covers skill structure, YAML frontmatter, trigger types (keywords, intent patterns, file paths, content patterns), enforcement levels (block, suggest, warn), hook mechanisms (UserPromptSubmit, PreToolUse), session tracking, and the 500-line rule.</description>
    <location>skills/skill-developer/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>sync-schemas</name>
    <description>Re-analyze the official anthropics/claude-plugins-official marketplace and update local JSON Schemas. Use when user says 'sync schemas', 'update schemas', or 'refresh schemas'.</description>
    <location>skills/sync-schemas/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>tailwindcss</name>
    <description>Tailwind CSS v4 utility-first styling patterns including responsive design, dark mode, and custom configuration. Use when styling with Tailwind, adding utility classes, configuring Tailwind, setting up dark mode, or customizing the theme.</description>
    <location>skills/tailwindcss/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>task-check</name>
    <description>Verify task completion before finishing work. Agent-driven skill that checks acceptance criteria, catches incomplete work, bugs, and quality issues. Spawn with task ID, location, and work summary.</description>
    <location>skills/task-check/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>web-design-guidelines</name>
    <description>Review UI code for Web Interface Guidelines compliance. Use when asked to "review my UI", "check accessibility", "audit design", "review UX", or "check my site against best practices".</description>
    <location>skills/web-design-guidelines/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
  <skill>
    <name>writing-tests</name>
    <description>Use this skill when writing, reviewing, or improving tests. Trigger on: 'write tests', 'add tests', 'test naming', 'what should I test', 'edge cases', 'test structure', 'assertion', 'toBe vs toEqual', 'toBeDefined', 'toBeTruthy', 'test review', 'test quality', 'test coverage', 'how to test', 'bug found write test', 'one test enough', 'test name', 'arrange act assert', 'AAA pattern'. Also trigger when user shares a test and asks for review, asks about assertion best practices, asks what edge cases to consider, mentions test names like 'test login' or 'should work', asks about splitting tests, or reports finding a bug and wants to know what else to test. Do NOT trigger for test runner configuration (jest.config, vitest.config), CI/CD pipeline setup, or questions about testing frameworks that aren't about how to write the tests themselves.</description>
    <location>skills/writing-tests/SKILL.md</location>
  </skill>
</available_skills>
